<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TripApplication</string>
    <string name="ZL">Welcome to ZL Travel Agency!</string>
    <string name="click1"><![CDATA[Click to enter -->]]></string>
    <string name="click2">About US</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_aboutus">ScrollingActivity_aboutus</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="About_us" />
    <string name="content">ZL Travel Agency is a new company which committing to providing customers with a better travel experice.
        Our object is providing careful travel planning, customers can choose suitable and favorite tourist attractions according to our introduction of various famous tourist attractions.
        We will introduce the unique features of each scenic spot according to the actual situation, as well as the surrounding environment, including accommodation, food and so on.
        We will also attach pictures of each scenic spot for you to choose from. We hope you can choose our service, we will let you have a perfect trip.
    </string>
    <string name="rdo_home_lable">首页</string>
    <string name="rdo_service_lable">服务</string>
    <string name="rdo_help_lable">帮助</string>
    <string name="lable_home">Country and region</string>
    <string name="lable_China">1.China</string>
    <string name="lable_South_Kroea">2.South Kroea</string>
    <string name="lable_USA">The United State</string>
    <string name="lable_France">4.France</string>
    <string name="lable_USA2">3.The United States</string>
    <string name="lable_UK">5.The United Kindom</string>
    <string name="lable_Japan">6.Japan</string>
    <string name="lable_India">7.India</string>
    <string name="lable_Australia">8.Australia</string>
    <string-array name="China">
        <item>Beijing</item>
        <item>Shanghai</item>
        <item>Guangzhou</item>
        <item>Chengdu</item>
        <item>Hong Kong</item>
        <item>Taiwan</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="South_Korea">
        <item>Seoul</item>
        <item>Busan</item>
        <item>Inchon</item>
        <item>Daegu</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="USA">
        <item>New York</item>
        <item>Los Angeles</item>
        <item>Chicago</item>
        <item>Houston</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="France">
        <item>Paris</item>
        <item>Marseille</item>
        <item>Lyon</item>
        <item>Nice</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="UK">
        <item>London</item>
        <item>Edinburgh</item>
        <item>Cardiff</item>
        <item>Liverpool</item>
        <item>Oxford</item>
        <item>Cambridge</item>
        <item>Manchester</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Japan">
        <item>Tokyo</item>
        <item>Yokohama</item>
        <item>Osaka</item>
        <item>Nagoya</item>
        <item>Kobe</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="India">
        <item>Bombay</item>
        <item>Delhi</item>
        <item>Bangalore</item>
        <item>Kolkata</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Australia">
        <item>Sydney</item>
        <item>Canberra</item>
        <item>Perth</item>
        <item>Darwin</item>
        <item>Melbourne</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Beijing1">Beijing, hereinafter referred to as \"jing\", is a provincial-level administrative region of the People\'s Republic of China, the capital, and municipalities directly under the central government, national center city, very large cities, the national political center, cultural center and international communication center, science and technology innovation center, is the world famous ancient capital and modern international city, is the central committee of the communist party of China, the central people\'s government of the People\'s Republic of China and the National People\'s Congress standing committee\'s office is located.Beijing is located in north China, with its center at 116°20 \'east longitude and 39°56\' north latitude. It adjoins tianjin in the east and hebei in the rest. The total area of Beijing is 16,410.54 square kilometers.Beijing terrain northwest high, southeast low. Mountains surround the west, north and northeast, and the southeast is a plain that slopes gently toward the bohai sea. The main rivers flowing through the territory are yongding river, chaobai river, north canal, and tuma river, etc. Most of them originate from the mountains in the northwest, run through the mountains, wind through the plain areas in the southeast, and finally merge into the bohai sea respectively. Beijing has a typical warm temperate semi-humid continental monsoon climate, with high temperature and rainy summer, cold and dry winter and short spring and autumn.</string>
    <string name="Tiananmen">Tian \'anmen, the largest urban center square in the world, is the symbol of Beijing and even the whole China. Everyone in China must have \"witnessed\" its glory, but it is still exciting to be in it. Tian \'anmen rostrum is located in the north end of the square, the five-star red flag flying high above the square; The monument to the people\'s heroes stands in the middle of the square; The great hall of the people and the national museum of China are on opposite sides of the square. Chairman MAO memorial hall and zhengyang gate tower stand in the south of the square. Tian \'anmen square is a must-see place for almost all tourists, as well as a place for Beijing residents to relax. Skateboarding teenagers are often seen here, and kite dancing (especially in spring and autumn) is also a big sight. On major festivals, the square may hold rallies, set off fireworks, display flower beds or parade.</string>
    <string name="Changcheng">The Great Wall, stretching thousands of miles from east to west; It has been built for more than 2,000 years. By climbing, partial to the cliff to nowhere, we can see the construction of its strange hardships. Its magnificent charm, aesthetic value, defensive function and military strategy are rare in the cultural legacy of the world. It is the miracle of the world, is a great miracle, because it is deeply admired and admired by the people of all countries. Standing on the Great Wall, whether it is spring flowers, autumn moon, summer clouds and winter snow, or see the Great Wall inside and outside the vast mountains, even the decline of the day grass, there is a strong sense of nostalgia. Perhaps, we have forgotten the ancient battlefield flying hu jia jige drum, flashing sword, but we will not forget in the last two thousand years to build thousands of ancestors of the Great Wall. Their amazing intelligence, incredible perseverance and amazing creativity not only shocked us, but also inspired us.</string>
    <string name="Gugong">Beijing Palace Museum is the imperial palace of Ming and qing dynasties in China, formerly known as the Forbidden City, located in the center of the central axis of Beijing, is the essence of ancient Chinese palace architecture. Beijing Palace Museum to three main halls as the center, covers an area of 720,000 square meters, the construction area of about 150,000 square meters, there are more than 70 large and small palaces, more than 9,000 houses. It is one of the largest and most complete ancient wooden structures in the world.The Forbidden City in Beijing began construction in the fourth year of yongle (1406), based on the nanjing Palace Museum, until the 18th year of yongle (1420). It is a rectangular city, north and south 961 meters long, east and west 753 meters wide, surrounded by 10 meters high wall, outside there is 52 meters wide moat. The buildings inside the Forbidden City are divided into two parts: the outer court and the inner court. The center of the outer dynasty was the hall of supreme harmony, the hall of zhonghe and the hall of baohe, collectively known as the three main halls, where the state held a great ceremony. The center of the inner court is the dry qing palace, the house of Thailand, the palace of earthly tranquility, collectively known as the rear three palace, is the emperor and queen living in the palace.</string>
    <string name="Yiheyuan">The Summer Palace, formerly known as the garden of clear ripples, is located in the western outskirts of Beijing. It is based on kunming lake, wanshou mountain as the site, to the west lake in hangzhou as the blueprint, from the jiangnan garden design techniques and built a large landscape garden, is also the most complete preservation of a royal palace garden, known as the \"royal garden museum\", is also a national key tourist attractions.Before emperor qianlong of the qing dynasty took over the throne, four large imperial gardens were built in the western suburbs of Beijing. In the 15th year of qianlong\'s reign (1750), emperor qianlong used 4.48 million taillons of silver to change it into a garden of clear ripples, which formed a royal garden area of 20 kilometers from present qinghua garden to fragrant hill. In the tenth year of xianfeng (1860), qingyi garden was burned down by the anglo-french allied forces. Guangxu 14 years (1888) reconstruction, renamed the Summer Palace, as summer recreation. Guangxu twenty-sixth year (1900), the Summer Palace was destroyed by the \"eight allied forces\", the treasures were looted. After the fall of the qing dynasty, the Summer Palace was destroyed again during the period of warlord warfare and kuomintang rule.</string>
    <string name="lable_click">please select the city you want:</string>
    <string name="lable_Tiananmen">Tiananmen</string>
    <string name="lable_changcheng">The Great Wall</string>
    <string name="lable_huhong">Beijing Palace Museum</string>
    <string name="lable_yiheyuan">The Summer Palace</string>
    <string name="lable1">Beijing</string>
    <string name="lable2">Shanghai</string>
    <string name="lable3">Chengdu</string>
    <string name="lable4">Hong Kong</string>
    <string name="lable5">Taiwan</string>
    <string name="btnChina">China</string>
    <string name="btnKroea">Kroea</string>
    <string name="btnUSA">USA</string>
    <string name="btnFrance">France</string>
    <string name="btnUK">UK</string>
    <string name="btnJapan">Japan</string>
    <string name="btnIndia">India</string>
    <string name="btnAustralia">Australia</string>
    <string name="Shanghai1">Shanghai, the largest city in China and one of the municipalities directly under the central government of the People\'s Republic of China, is the national center of China and a prosperous international metropolis. It is located at the mouth of the Yangtze river, facing the east China sea, facing kyushu island of Japan, facing hangzhou bay in the south, and facing jiangsu and zhejiang provinces in the west. Shanghai has a subtropical humid monsoon climate with four distinct seasons. January is the coldest month with an average temperature of 4.9℃, while July is usually the hottest month with an average temperature of 30.9℃. Shanghai has a profound modern urban culture and numerous historical sites. The traditional culture of wu and yue in the south of the Yangtze river has merged with the diverse culture brought by immigrants from all over the country, forming a unique Shanghai culture.Shanghai is a national famous historical and cultural city, with 19 national key cultural relic protection units, 136 Shanghai cultural relic protection units and 4 city-level historic and cultural towns in Shanghai.</string>
    <string name="zhonggongyidahuizhi">The first national congress of the communist party of China (CPC) is the birthplace of the CPC. The meeting site is located at 76 xingye road (no. 106 wangzhi road), Shanghai. It is an old shikumen residential building with brick and wood structure at the bottom and the first floor along the street. The site of the CPC national congress was listed by the state council as one of the first batch of national key cultural relics under protection and a national patriotism education demonstration base. In September 2016, it was included in the \"first batch of China\'s 20th century architectural heritage\" list.</string>
    <string name="chenghuangmiao">Shanghai chenghuang Temple (the City God Temple of Shanghai), its history dates back over 600 years, starting from the Ming dynasty was built to contemporary through vicissitudes of life, Shanghai chenghuang Temple has become Shanghai\'s famous tourist attractions, as a Taoist Temple, Shanghai chenghuang Temple has a long history and enjoys a high reputation both at home and abroad, with the development of the economy, has become the Shanghai on the above, small snacks chenghuang Temple Taoist Temple, the City God Temple, yuyuan garden ring around, present a Shanghai chenghuang Temple culture.Cheng huang, also known as cheng huang god, was one of the important gods worshiping in ancient Chinese religious culture. Most of the gods were famous ministers and heroes who had made contributions to the local people.</string>
    <string name="daguanyuan">Shanghai grand view garden is located at no. 701, qingshang road, qingpu district, Shanghai. It is located at the west side of dianshan lake, 65 kilometers away from Shanghai urban area. Originally named dianshan lake scenic area, it was renamed Shanghai grand view garden in 1991, covering an area of 1500 mu. It is the key unit of Shanghai spiritual civilization construction, and after repeated renovation and expansion, it is a comprehensive amusement park integrating sightseeing, tourism and leisure.Shanghai grand view garden is a large-scale archaized garden designed according to the description of Chinese qing dynasty classic dream of red mansions. The garden complex is planned and designed by liang yousong, Shanghai garden courtyard. The overall layout takes the grand view building as the main body, from \"the provincial relatives villa\" the stone archway, the stone lantern, qinfang lake, the body ren mu DE, the winding path leads to you, the palace gate, \"the too empty illusion\" the relief screen wall, the wooden archway and so on forms the whole garden central axis. In the west, there are yihong courtyard, loncui nunnery, pear fragrant courtyard and marble fang. In the east, there are more than 20 groups of architectural scenic spots such as xiaoxiang pavilion, heng wu hospital, polygonum wind house and daoxiang village.</string>
    <string name="yuyuan">Yu Garden is located in the northeast of the old city of Shanghai, with fuyou road in the north, anren street in the east and old town god\'s temple in the southwest.In the garden, there are three famous stone known as the jade linglong, in the south of the Yangtze river, the command post of the small sword uprising in 1853 point spring hall, the side of the garden has the town god\'s temple and shop street and other tourist attractions.Yuyuan garden was opened to the public in 1961 and was listed by the state council as a national key cultural relic protection unit in 1982.</string>
    <string name="chengdu_introduce">Chengdu, a prefecture-level city under the jurisdiction of sichuan province, rong for short, nicknamed \"rong city, jincheng\", is the capital of sichuan province, vice provincial city, mega city, western war zone organ resident, the state council identified as an important high-tech industrial base, business and logistics center and comprehensive transportation hub, is an important central city in the western region. In 2018, the city has jurisdiction over 20 districts (cities) and counties, high-tech zone and chengdu direct administrative zone of tianfu new zone, covering an area of 14,335 square kilometers, with a permanent population of 16.33 million and a GDP of 1,534.277 billion yuan.</string>
    <string name="dujiangyan">Dujiangyan is located in guankou town, dujiangyan city, chengdu city. It is a large-scale water conservancy project built in ancient China and still in use today. It is known as \"the originator of world water conservancy culture\" and is a famous tourist resort in China. Dujiangyan water conservancy project was built by li bing, governor of shu county of the state of qin and his sons in the 59th year (256 years before) of king zhou. It is the oldest and only water conservancy project in the world characterized by no dam to divert water. It is also a world cultural heritage.</string>
    <string name="daxiongmaojidi">Chengdu research base of giant panda breeding is one of the main research bases for the Chinese government to carry out the relocation protection project of giant pandas and other endangered wild animals. It is a famous research institution in China and even the world for the protection and research of rare and endangered wild animals, including the giant panda, which integrates the research and breeding of giant pandas, conservation education, education and tourism, and the construction of panda culture.</string>
    <string name="wuhouci">Wuhou temple museum is a famous cultural shrine of The Three Kingdoms at home and abroad. Wuhou temple is the most famous monument of zhuge liang and liu bei and the only emperor and minister worship temple in China. It is also the most influential relic museum of The Three Kingdoms in China. Wuhou temple was built in 223 years, mainly composed of huiling temple, zhaolei temple of han dynasty and wuhou temple. It is one of the first batch of national key cultural relics protection units with ancient and elegant environment and magnificent temple.</string>
    <string name="dufucaotang">Du fu cottage is the former residence of du fu, a tang dynasty poet in chengdu. The poet du fu moved to chengdu in 759 and spent three years and nine months writing more than 240 poems here. The main buildings are grand palace, poetry hall, chaimen, gongbu temple and shaoling cottage. The cottage museum collects more than 30,000 volumes of historical materials and more than 2,000 cultural relics, which are valuable materials for studying du fu, the \"master of poetry\". Du fu cottage is the first batch of national key cultural relics protection units.</string>
    <string name="HKintroduce">Hong Kong (Hong Kong), hereinafter referred to as \"Hong Kong\" (HK), the full name of the Hong Kong special administrative region of the People\'s Republic of China, is located in the south of China, the east of pearl river mouth, macau, China and the west across the sea, north and neighbouring shenzhen, zhuhai wanshan islands in the south, an area including Hong Kong island, Kowloon, New Territories, and around 262 islands, total land area of 1106.34 square kilometers, sea area of 1648.69 square kilometers. By the end of 2018, the total population was about 7.4825 million, making it one of the regions with the highest population density in the world and the highest life expectancy in the world.</string>
    <string name="weiduoliya">Victoria harbour, or Victoria harbour for short, is the harbour between Hong Kong island and Kowloon Peninsula in the Hong Kong special administrative region. Hong Kong is known as the \"pearl of the Orient\", \"three of the world\'s best natural harbors\" and \"three of the world\'s best night spots\" due to its wide width and deep water. The name of Victoria harbor comes from queen Victoria of England. Free access throughout the year. In his early years, he was regarded by the British as having the potential to become an excellent port in east Asia. Later, he won Hong Kong from the qing government and developed the maritime trade in the far east. Victoria harbour has always influenced the history and culture of Hong Kong and dominated the development of Hong Kong\'s economy and tourism. It is one of the keys for Hong Kong to become an international metropolis.</string>
    <string name="dishini">Hong Kong Disneyland is located in lantau island, New Territories, Hong Kong is the world\'s smallest Disneyland, is also China\'s first Disneyland, theme park is divided into seven park, respectively: main street USA, adventureland, fantasyland and tomorrowland, toy story stronghold, grizzly bear valley and blurred manor, the grizzlies valley and blurred manor is unique in the world, full of fantasy, Hong Kong Disneyland theme song \"let the magic fly\" by the honorary ambassador to Disney Hong Kong singer Jacky cheung, brisk melody, you can feel full of happiness from the music.</string>
    <string name="sea_park">Hong Kong Ocean Park, with its Marine aquarium and theme park, is the favorite place for visitors to Hong Kong. Here you can not only see interesting amusement park, dolphin show, but also a variety of strange Marine fish, towering ocean skyscraper tower, more exciting over the mine flying car, speed trip, can be called the perfect combination of science, tourism, entertainment.</string>
    <string name="taiwan">Alishan, Sun Moon Lake, taroko gorge, jade mountain, kenting, yangming mountain are all famous natural tourist attractions in Taiwan. Jiufen old street, ruifang district, xinbei city, beitou district, Taipei city, lugang town, changhua county, yingge district, xinbei city, etc. The territory has many characteristics of hot springs, hot spring culture unique.</string>
    <string name="alishan">The sunrise, sea of clouds, sunset, forest and alpine railway of alishan are collectively known as the five wonders of alishan. Alishan railway has a history of more than 70 years and is one of the only three remaining alpine railways in the world. In particular, the zigzag climb around the third helix and the first lane is an unforgettable experience. Zhushan is the best place to watch the sunrise. To zhushan, you can take the train or follow the steps from the flagstone road next to the telecom office.</string>
    <string name="riyuetan">Sun Moon Lake is the most famous scenic spot on Taiwan island. Located in nantou county in the west, it is the second largest and largest natural lake in Taiwan province, lying on the top of the mountains between mt. Jade and mt. Ali. Shore perimeter 35 kilometers, covers an area of 7.7 ㎞ squared, water depth and 30 metres. The water surface is slightly larger than the famous west lake in hangzhou, but the water depth is more than 10 times that of the west lake. The Sun Moon Lake was originally two separate lakes, but was dammed downstream to generate electricity. As the water level rose, the two lakes became one.</string>
    <string name="seoulintroduce">Seoul was the capital of the Korean dynasty for 600 years and has many historical sites. The palaces, jongmyong temples and other buildings of the Korean period were jingfu palace, changde palace, myung court, changgyeong palace, gyeonghee palace, deshou palace, yunhyeon palace, jongmyong temple, sheji palace, sungyeon hall, namdaemun gate, dongdaemun gate, Seoul city wall, south han mountain city, north han mountain city, zhenling tomb, hongling tomb, xuanjing tomb, xianren tomb, taikang tomb and so on. Other historical sites include tucheng of dream village, fengna tucheng, saga mountain city, tomb of six dead ministers, bong en temple, bong yuan temple, cao xi temple -- presidential residence of South Korea -- blue house, independent gate, Ming dong tian cathedral, etc.</string>
    <string name="jingfugong">Gyeongbuk palace is the palace of the joseon dynasty (1392~1910) in Seoul, South Korea. It is also the official palace of the joseon dynasty. It is the palace of the new dynasty built during the joseon dynasty\'s migration and has a history of 500 years. In the book of songs in ancient China, there was a poem called \"junzi wannian, jie er jingfu\". This hall is named because it is located in the north of Seoul, also known as \"beique\". Gyeongbok palace is one of the largest and oldest palaces in Seoul and the political center of the late feudal society in South Korea.</string>
    <string name="litaiyuan">Litawon street, located in the lung mountain district of Seoul, is the most exotic place in Seoul, where you can experience and understand the comprehensive culture through food, entertainment and shopping. Shopping street pear Thai courtyard\'s international visibility is how high, from this \"do not know Seoul is not strange, do not know pear Thai courtyard is strange\" the saying, we can be clear. Usually referred to as the 1.4-kilometre-long section from the 1st hole to the 2nd hole in the hannan river, it is not only home to numerous shops, but also a variety of entertainment facilities and gourmet restaurants. One of the main features of the street is the widespread use of English. Not only are koreans walking along the road talking with foreigners in English, but the signs of shops along the road are marked in English.</string>
    <string name="lable21">Seoul</string>
    <string name="lable22">Busan</string>
    <string name="lable23">inchon</string>
    <string name="lable24">daegu</string>
    <string name="fushan">Busan tourism roughly divided into coastal tourism and inland tourism two parts. Coastal tourism mainly refers to bathing beaches, islands, Marine parks, etc., while inland tourism refers to busan city, historical sites, jinjing mountain city, Vatican temple, donglai township school, dongsan hole shell mound, busan World Cup stadium, BEXCO, etc. There are sea beach yuntai sea beach, guanganli sea beach, songting sea beach and so on. In addition, busan Marine natural history museum, fuquan museum, busan municipal art museum and fusan museum and other cultural sites.</string>
    <string name="weishanyan">Ulsan rock consists of six granite peaks, with a circumference of 4 kilometers. Climb ulsan rock, you can see the snow yue mountain scenery and the east China sea, damo peak, hexaping reservoir area. There are three legends about the origin of the name of ulsan rock: first, it is called \"ulsan\" (south Korean grammar is similar) because of the emergence of the fence road; second, it is taken from the place name of ulsan in gyeongsang south; and third, it is said that \"crying mountain\" is translated into Chinese in Korean.</string>
    <string name="longtoushangongyuan">Longtoushan, also known as \"dragon head rock\", the mountain is shaped like a cloud-driven dragon flying into the air from the sea, as the name suggests, it is called \"longtoushan\". Here can enjoy the beautiful seascape and the surrounding beautiful scenery, in the sunset afterglow, appears to have the emotional appeal all the more. In the park, a representative building busan tower is built, which symbolizes the long and long history and culture of busan.</string>
    <string name="inchonintroduce">As a port city with the ocean, incheon has many famous Marine scenic spots. Located in the qianhai of incheon, wuyi island and ishi wei island are the shooting places of classic Korean dramas such as stairway to heaven, sad love song, and ishi wei island. They are also famous islands frequented by tourists. The cultural street on yuewei island, north cheng dong, central district is also one of the famous scenic spots</string>
    <string name="yueweidao">Yuemei island was once an island about 1 km away from the incheon qianhai before gradually connecting with the land in the process of road building. The moon tail island gets its name from the shape of the half-moon tail island. Yuemei island, not far from Seoul, has convenient transportation and is often visited by tourists on weekends. Yuemei island has cafes, sashimi shops, restaurants and so on. Enjoying the beautiful scenery of the western sea and savoring delicious food is a real treat. There are more than 50 sashimi shops on the island, which carefully prepare delicious seafood for tourists. In addition, the culture street with a length of 1200 meters extends all the way from graffiti pillars, meeting places, art fields and public performances. Here, public performances follow, and street painters improvise for visitors. Yuemei island must go to the amusement park. While not comparable to other large-scale theme parks, amusement parks are known for their Apollo disco and pirate ships. Exciting pirate ships attract tourists from all over the country, and Apollo disco even just to see people feel endless fun. From yuemei island you can also take a cruise around the beautiful scenery. Cool sea breeze, clear western sea water, and hovering over the seagull, all let a person intoxicated.</string>
    <string name="chuandengsi">Lantern temple is located in dingu mountain, is a thousand years old temple. According to legend, it was built by a monk in the koguryo period, and was named as the lantern temple after the jade lanterns were donated to Buddha by the zhen and princess of the Korean king of the faithful (1274-1308). There are many things worth seeing in chuandeng temple, such as daxiong temple (no. 178 protected cultural relic) and yaoshi temple (no. 179 protected cultural relic). In particular, there are strange statues in the main hall that cannot be seen in other temples, namely, the naked woman under the eaves and the figures on the pillars. The roof is \"well algae\" style, surrounded by colorful sculptures and lotus flowers, flying apsaras and other patterns. In the courtyard of the mountain temple, there is a Vatican bell of the song dynasty, 1.6 meters high and 1 meter in diameter. The lantern temple is not only beautiful in itself, but also famous for its surrounding landscape. Especially in the early morning and evening to view the sea, the scenery is very spectacular. Lantern temple is famous in Korea for watching sunsets. There is also a bamboo garden where you can take a rest.</string>
    <string name="daegu">Daegu is the fourth largest city in South Korea after Seoul, busan and incheon. Shopping and cultural arts, food shops and other modern charm and long historical sites coexist, can be a multi-cultural experience of the city - daegu.You can enjoy a variety of dynamic Tours here, such as sightseeing of famous products, visiting of delicious food and self-cultivation experience.</string>
    <string name="bagongshan">Badong mountain is a peak from the center of daegu area to yongchuan city, junwei county, etc. The mountain is not very high. The distance from the entrance of the hiking trail to the seated statue of guofeng stone Buddha at the top of shamaoyan mountain is 2.1km. It is entered from the left side of the entrance of guanyan temple (zhongge). Badong mountain is also one of the centers of buddhist culture, including tonghua temple, yuguanfeng stone Buddha statue, yuanxiao temple, qiansheng temple, buddhist grottoes temple and other numerous temples and buddhist cultural relics. The scenery of the badong mountain is pleasant and beautiful. Here cuckoos are in full bloom in spring, trees are green in summer, mountains are full of maple in autumn, and snow and ice are crystal clear in winter.</string>
    <string name="yiyao">The museum is located in daegu yaling, which was opened in 1993. It is a comprehensive cultural space + museum. It tells the history of daegu yaling and some knowledge of Korean medicinal materials. Most guides and electronic presentations are in four languages (including Chinese). Here you can not only take photos in person, but also participate in cutting Korean medicinal materials, making Korean aromatic agent, Korean foot soup and other experience projects.</string>
    <string name="ny0">New York City is home to many world-class galleries and performing arts competitions, making it one of the cultural and entertainment centers of the western hemisphere. New York is also known as \"the city that never sleeps\" because of its 24-hour subway system and its never-ending crowds. New York is an unparalleled entertainment city in the world. Ballet, classical music, opera, large-scale concert, jazz music, swing dance; Plays, movies, cabaret operas, discos, piano performances, you name it, are lively and exciting. It is particularly worth pointing out that all this is world-class. New York\'s romantic nightlife is also worth looking forward to.</string>
    <string name="ny1">For more than a century, the bronze statue of the goddess of liberty standing on the island of liberty has become a symbol of friendship between the American nation and the French people, forever expressing the lofty ideal of the American people for democracy and freedom. Passengers on ships entering New York harbor can see the statue of liberty standing tall and carrying the liberty torch. For thousands of immigrants to the United States, the statue of liberty was a guarantee of freedom from the poverty and oppression of the old world.</string>
    <string name="ny2">Manhattan is described as the economic and cultural center of the whole United States. It is home to the central business district of New York City. It has the highest concentration of skyscrapers in the world. Wall Street in Manhattan is the most important financial center in the world, with the New York stock exchange and nasdaq. Manhattan\'s real estate market is also one of the most expensive in the world.</string>
    <string name="lable31">new york</string>
    <string name="lable32">los angeles</string>
    <string name="lable33">chicago</string>
    <string name="lable34">houston</string>
    <string name="la0">Los Angeles, located in southwestern California, is the second largest city in the United States and the largest city in the western United States. Los Angeles has an area of about 1,291 square kilometers, and its urban center coordinates are 34°03 \'north latitude and 118°15\' west longitude. The city has a population of about 3,976 million (2016). In 2016, the regional GDP of Los Angeles was $753.1 billion. It is one of the important centers for business, international trade, science, education, entertainment and sports in the United States, and one of the major bases for the petrochemical, Marine, aerospace and electronics industries in the United States.</string>
    <string name="la1">Hollywood is the world\'s most famous movie, television, entertainment and travel destination, located in the northwest suburbs of Los Angeles, California, USA. First discovered by photographers looking for locations, the site attracted many photographers around the beginning of the 20th century, and has since become a film hub for small companies and independent filmmakers seeking to escape patent control.</string>
    <string name="la2">Universal studios in cutscenes serve universal studios theme park is famous for Los Angeles, not only have many rides like a movie set again, and an adjunct to the universal studios city walk, all the shops, restaurants, cinemas in bright colours, modelling and lively giant signs to attract tourists, let visitors step into universal studios, immediately enjoy the intense stimulation visual sense. In order to expand the studio, the film giant CarlLaemmle moved his studio from Hollywood to a larger site in 1915. He designed the universal tour, which has been taking tourists around the world for 25 years.</string>
    <string name="chi0">Chicago is located in the center of the north American continent, with its urban center coordinates of 41°39 \'north latitude and 87°34\' west longitude. It is the largest business center and one of the largest futures markets in the United States, and the number of new enterprises in its metropolitan area has been ranked the first in the United States, ranking as the most balanced economy in the United States. In addition, Chicago also has many world-famous tall buildings, known as the \"hometown of skyscrapers\".</string>
    <string name="chi1">Chicago grant park is the most important downtown park in Chicago, located between Michigan avenue and lake Michigan. Grant park connects downtown Chicago with lake Michigan, elevating the Chicago skyline and cityscape, and enhancing the leisure function of busy Chicago. It covers an area of 1.29 square kilometers.</string>
    <string name="chi2">The robey house is a masterpiece of Wright\'s prairie style architecture, described as \"the cornerstone of modern architecture\". Robey\'s house has the qualities of a standard prairie building, and the structure is completely asymmetrical, looking like blocks of all shapes and sizes, yet the overall visual harmony is incredible. There are 174 stained-glass Windows and doors, which you can see in an hour-long group tour.</string>
    <string name="hou0">Houston is known around the world for its energy (especially oil), aviation industry and canals. The port of Houston is the sixth largest port in the world and the busiest port in the United States. Fortune 500 headquarters is second only to New York City. Houston is home to the Texas medical center, the world\'s largest and most important research and treatment facility. Houston also has the lowest cost of living and home prices of 27 major metropolitan areas with a population of more than 1.7 million. Houston is called a \"global city\" by the globalization and world cities study group and network.</string>
    <string name="hou1">Located on the edge of Herman park, the miller amphitheater offers high quality free performances or movies every weekend (five, six or three days) from the end of April to the end of November: symphony, ballet, cabaret, jazz, Spanish, etc. The Shakespeare Festival runs from late July to mid-august.</string>
    <string name="hou2">In the eastern suburb of Houston, outside the entrance of the Houston harbor channel off route 8. In April 1836, general Santa Anna of Mexico pursued the rebels led by Sam Houston, only to be attacked by Sam Houston. Within a few minutes Santa Anna\'s army had surrendered. It wasn\'t a big fight, it was independence for Texas. Next to the old battlefield lies the uss Texas. The ship is the only surviving warship to have fought in the first and second world wars.</string>
    <string name="lable41">paris</string>
    <string name="lable42">marseille</string>
    <string name="lable43">lyon</string>
    <string name="lable44">nice</string>
</resources>
